<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<atom:link href='http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml'/>
<generator>
clj-rss
</generator>
<title>
Podcasts Notes
</title>
<link>
http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes
</link>
<description>
Notes from interesting podcasts
</description>
<lastBuildDate>
Mon, 16 Feb 2015 22:26:28 +1100
</lastBuildDate>
<author>
mokagio
</author>
<item>
<guid>
http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes/podcasts-notes/posts/2015-02-16-hack-the-entrepreneur-058.html
</guid>
<link>
http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes/podcasts-notes/posts/2015-02-16-hack-the-entrepreneur-058.html
</link>
<title>
Hack the Entrepreneur 58
</title>
<description>
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href='http://hacktheentrepreneur.com/sunni-brown/'&gt;&quot;58: Sunni Brown on Refusing to Scale and Being Kind to Others&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;To lead a good life as an entrepreneur your business needs &lt;strong&gt;core values&lt;/strong&gt;, lines that you won't cross, projects that you won't take, clients you're not gonna work with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;core values&lt;/strong&gt; theme reminds me of the &lt;i&gt;&quot;am I acting like a ...&quot;&lt;/i&gt; guideline form the &quot;6 months to 6 figures&quot; book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also connects with the &lt;a href='http://developingperspective.com/2015/02/11/211/'&gt;latest Developing Perspective episode&lt;/a&gt; where David Smith talks about the honesty in the marketing messages for the apps on the App Store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another take away is that you shouldn't be harsh with your ideas. It's fine to have a ton of new ideas every day, and they should all be looked at in the same way. The key is then in being honest and focusing only on those that actually sound good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<pubDate>
Mon, 16 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +1100
</pubDate>
<author>
mokagio
</author>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes/podcasts-notes/posts/2015-02-15-giantrobots-132-job-stories.html
</guid>
<link>
http://mokagio.github.io/podcasts-notes/podcasts-notes/posts/2015-02-15-giantrobots-132-job-stories.html
</link>
<title>
Giant Robots 132
</title>
<description>
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href='http://giantrobots.fm/132'&gt;&quot;132: Story Tellers&quot;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The episode is about the conversion from user stories to &lt;a href='http://alanklement.blogspot.com.au/2013/09/replacing-user-story-with-job-story.html'&gt;job stories&lt;/a&gt; in Thoughtbots, and the positive effects it brought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from the concept of job story a big insight from this episode is the methodology Thoughtbots uses to introduce changes in their workflow. They have a research Trello board where every employee can suggest experiments, saying why that particular approach is working for them, and why they think it would help the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really like this scientific approach to experiment and improvement. Never assume that what works for other people will actually work for you, and never think that your current way of doing things is the best one. There is always room for improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another interesting takeaway from the episode is the misconception on velocity, and how hard it is to communicate to management what it really is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally probably the most important key of the Agile manifesto comes up as well: &quot;People over process&quot;, which is many times forgotten in agencies that sell themselves a Agile.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<pubDate>
Sun, 15 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +1100
</pubDate>
<author>
mokagio
</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
